Previously on White Collar...
"妙警賊探" 前情提要...
The Mosconi Codex.
莫斯克尼法典
This is no ordinary book.
這可不是一般的書
- Neal. - Hello,Rebecca.
- Neal - 你好 Rebecca
You two know each other?
你們倆認識?
I swear,I had my key card when I left work.
我發誓 員工卡下班的時候還在身上
We figure out what's hidden in those pages and get to it first.
我們找出那本書隱藏的秘密 然後先下手為強
I'm the reason the thief got in.
我是那個賊能進來的原因
My hope was that the owner would let us study and look at the Codex,and now it's gone.
我本希望收藏家能讓我們近距離 研究一下法典 但是現在不行了
David Siegel.Cause of death was a gunshot wound to the sternum.
David Siegel 死因為胸部中槍
And we're no closer to figuring out who did this and why.
而我們對於誰幹的 為什麼這麼干 毫無頭緒
Dr.Summers,I need your help.
Summers醫生 我需要你的幫助
Just because a person starts doing good things doesn't mean he wants to stop doing bad things.
就因為一個人開始做好事 可不意味著他想停止做壞事
I've been serving too many masters.
我是太多人的牽線木偶了
I'm through being everyone's puppet.
所有人都在指揮我的行動
Which strings,exactly,do you plan on cutting?
那麼準確來說 你想切掉那條線?
All of them.
所有的
I****
很不錯
Even the chip in the cover works.
連封皮裡的芯片都好使
How'd you pull that off?
你是怎麼做到的?
I don't make them.
我不管製作
I just sell them.
我只管銷售
You son of a bitch.
你個混蛋
Freeze!Hands in the air.
不許動! 舉起手來
FBI!Don't move!
FBI! 不許動!
He's all yours.
他是你的了
- What? - Don't "What" me.You know what.
- 怎麼了? - 別想糊弄我 你知道怎麼了
I gave you specific instructions.
我給你的命令很明確
"Sit down,make the deal,get arrested."Three out of three not good enough for you?
"坐下 交易 被捕"  我做得不夠好?
I don't remember mentioning anything about follow-up questions
我可不記得讓你提那些問題了
or interrogating the suspect before the arrest.
也沒讓你在疑犯被捕前就盤問他
Interrogating the suspect...What are you...What,the chip? - The chip.
- 審犯人... 你什麼... 什麼 芯片? - 芯片
I was gathering information. - For you or for us?
- 我在收集信息 - 為我們還是為你?
If I were up to something,you really think I'd do it when you had ears on me?
如果我在計劃什麼事 你真的認為我會在被監聽的時候做?
That's exactly when you'd do it.
你就是這麼做的
I have a feeling this is about more than passports.
我有種感覺 這不止護照那麼簡單
it's about passports.Also about the $2 million that went missing in the last case.
這就是關於護照 還有上個案子中失蹤的200萬美金
Dr.Summers might have some insight - into its location.
Summers醫生也許知道錢的位置
Dr.Summers had a tendency to take bad guys who wanna be good and turn them into worse guys.
Summers醫生就有那個能耐 把想洗心革面的壞人變得更壞
What exactly happened during your therapy session?
你做心理咨詢的時候 到底發什麼什麼事?
She encouraged me to be the man I really am.
她鼓勵我做真正的自己
I think Lucy told Charlie Brown that and only charged him 5￠.
我想Lucy也這麼告訴Charlie Brown了 但是人家只收了5分錢
And what kind of man might that be,exactly?
說實在的 你到底是什麼樣的人?
We were gonna discuss that at our next session.Now I have to wait 20 years.
這個問題我們下一療程再討論 現在我得再等20年
I think these belong to Jones.
我想這大概是Jones的
Hey,where'd you get all these?
嘿 這些都是你哪兒弄來的?
Confiscated in various busts around the city.Most in the last few weeks.
大多都是過去幾星期 全市各地抄查沒收來的
It's first-rate and identical.These were all made by the same person.
它們質量一流特徵相似 這些出自同一人之手
- You're sure about that? - Yeah,the eagle's eye.
- 你確定? - 是的 你看鷹眼
There's a tiny dot in the center of this one and in the one I bought from Ivan.
這本鷹眼中間有個小點 和我從Ivan手上買到的那本一樣
That dot is as good as a fingerprint.
這個點就相當於指紋了
So we're looking at a fairly large forgery operation.
所以我們尋找的是 一個相當大的偽造集團
You think Ivan's the artist?
你覺得Ivan是偽造師嗎?
No,he says he only sells them,and I believe him.
不是 他說他只負責賣 我相信他
Anyone this good would take credit.
能做這麼好的人是會邀功的
Think this has something to do with the uptick of crime in Little Odessa?
你認為這和小奧德賽區的 犯罪率上升有關係嗎?
I don't believe in coincidences.
我不相信巧合
Ivan's parking tickets.
Ivan的停車罰單
Ten so far this year,and they're all in the exact same spot.
今年已經十張了 而且都在同一個位置
I want traffic surveillance video for the past six months on that address.
我需要這條街上 過去六個月的監控錄像
Already on it.
已經在調了
- Really? - Really.
- 不是吧? - 是的
Same spot,day after day.
相同地點 每天都這樣
- Right in front of the hydrant.
就在消防栓跟前
There's plenty of metered parking down the street.
這條街上有很多計時收費停車位
Why risk another ticket?
為什麼甘冒被貼罰單的危險?
Doris Day parking.
Doris Day的停車位
I'm sorry.Doris Day what?
不好意思 Doris Day的什麼?
Spot right in front.
就在你眼前
The kind of parking Doris Day miraculously finds - in all her movies.
Doris Day在她的每部電影裡 都能神奇地找到的停車位
- I never knew you were a fan.
我從不知道你是她的影迷
Oh,I love 'em.
哦我愛死那些電影了
Place looks abandoned.
這地方看起來廢棄了
Yeah,not a bad spot for a passport forgery operation.
是啊 對於護照偽造集團來說不算糟
Let's get a warrant and check it out.
我們去弄張搜查令查一下
The history of cryptography...oddly cryptic.
密碼使用的歷史... 令人驚異地隱秘
Any luck finding out what type of code this is?
幸運的找到這是什麼類型密碼了嗎?
I've ruled out transposition and Caesar shifts.
我已經排除了移位式密碼和凱撒方陣
and Sudoku and Kenken.
哦 還有數獨以及聰明方格
Well,in a happy accident,you may have proven the Riemann Hypothesis.
說不定你無意中 還證明了黎曼假設呢
The only thing I've proven is that we need help.
我唯一能證明的是我們需要幫助
I've studied every pattern,every symbol.
我研究了每一個圖案 每一個符號
I can only conclude that it is of alien origin.
只能總結得出 這東西從外星來
I think you're right.
我覺得你是對的
Finally,you've come around.
你總算醒悟了
I think you're right.We need help.
我覺得你是對的 我們需要幫助
Well,I do know a monk in Berlin who dabbles in quantum mechanics.
我倒是認識一個柏林的修道士 他對量子力學有所涉獵
You think Hagen's using monks?
你覺得Hagen在利用修道士?
I think Hagen is using you.
我覺得Hagen在利用你
And me.
還有我
The only chance we have of getting a leg up on him is by deciphering the Codex first.
扳倒他的唯一機會是 我們率先破解出法典
- Until then... - It's ticking clocks and phone calls.
- 在那之前... - 倒計時中 需要咨詢無數人
All right,I gotta go. Peter and I are headed to Little Odessa.
好吧 我得走了 Peter和我要去小奧德賽
I do the talking.
我來說
We're just here on a routine visit. Nothing more.
我們是來常規檢查的 僅此而已
Well... doesn't look abandoned.
哦... 看來不像被廢棄了
Looks like someone brought it back to life.
看來有人重新啟用了這裡
Every time I see ice like this,I'm ten again.
每次我看到冰場就彷彿回到了童年
- Oh,she's good. - Yeah.
- 哦 滑得真不錯 - 是的
First Doris Day,now figure skating.
先是Doris Day 現在又是花樣滑冰
It's nice to see your softer side.
能看到你鐵漢柔情的一面 真是三生有幸
Who are you? What do you want?
你們是誰? 想要什麼?
We just have a few questions for the owner of this building.
我們只想問幾個問題 關於這座樓的主人
Put that away,or you'll get all of us killed.
趕緊收起來 要不然我們都有危險
This is private facility. You're trespassing.
這裡是私人領地 你們是非法侵入
I****
我覺得他們只是迷路了
Q***
別說話 Katya!
We just have a few questions.
我們只想問點事情
Questions for Katya,the talk of Little Odessa.
想問一下Katya 關於小奧德賽的事情
Neal Micali,sports agent.
Neal Micali 體育經紀人
I represent some of the world's top athletes.
我旗下有很多世界級運動員
This is Peter Nevins,figure skating coach to the stars.
這位是Peter Nevins 明星級花樣滑冰教練
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: Nancy 安 Zzinc 郭郭 塵沙 校對: 時差雪 時間軸: 靜靜的生活
white.collar.s05e06
妙警賊探 第五季 第 6 集
Peter Nevins,coach?
Peter Nevins 教練?
Never heard of you.
沒聽說過你
Really? You ever heard of Tara Lipinski? Or Michelle Kwan?
真的? 那你聽說過Tara Lipinski嗎? 還有Michelle Kwan?
They would be ushers at the ice capades if it weren't for this man.
要不是這個男人 他們現在就會在白雪溜冰團當引導員了
yes. He's just-- he's just-- I simply help them harness their own natural talents.
是的 他是 他只是 我只是幫他們挖掘了自身的潛能
Sorry to be wasting your time,but Katya has no interest in competing.
我不想浪費你的時間 但Katya對比賽沒有興趣
B***
Sergei 求你了 我想要一個新教練 我想比賽
-Thank you for your interest.
- 謝謝你的關注
- Now,if you'll excuse us... - It's not a problem.
- 那麼 容我們暫時告退... - 沒問題
We got another 20 girls to see by the end of the week,so... - 27
- 這周我們還需要見20個姑娘 所以... - 是27個
- Is it 27 now? - It's 27.
- 現在是27個了? - 是27
Listen...you're talented.Very talented.
聽著... 你很有才 非常有天賦
Don't give up on your dream.
請別放棄夢想
Sorry we wasted your time and ours.
很抱歉 耽誤了你我的時間
Wait.
等等
This is not the right time.
現在做出抉擇還為時過早
But don't choose another girl yet.
但暫時請別選擇其他姑娘
Here.
給
We'll be in touch.
咱們保持聯繫
- Figure skating coach?- What? You've been skating since you were a junior G-man.
- 花樣滑冰教練? - 怎麼? 你從還是個 菜鳥探員的時候就開始溜冰了呀
But that was hockey.We're talking body checks,not twirls.
但那是曲棍球 我們只會用身體撞人 而不是旋轉
come on.It's a good cover.
拜託 這是個很好的假身份
I don't need a cover.I could go in there with a tac team and turn that place upside down.
我不需要假身份 我可以帶著突擊隊闖進那兒翻個底朝天
Yeah,you could if you wanted to scare off the guys we're really after.
當然 如果你想要嚇跑我們想抓的傢伙 完全可以這麼做
Just admit it-- best way into this case is on skates.
承認吧 涉入此案的最好方式就是靠溜冰
You got a ticket.
你有張罰單
Come on,this is for your bio,not a mug shot.
拜託 這是拍簡歷照 不是入案照片
- Come on. - Oh,you're killing me.
- 快來吧 - 哦 你還不如殺了我
I don't have time for this.I've got ASAC work.
我沒時間幹這個 我得做助理特工主管的工作
- I can't play dress-up.- Just smile.
- 我不能玩盛裝打扮 - 微笑就好了
Rebecca?
Rebecca?
From the Gershon Museum.
來自Gershon博物館
Neal,from the FBI.
Neal 來自FBI
- How are you? - I'm,uh... terrible.
- 你近況如何? - 我... 很糟
The museum world,it's really small.
博物館的世界 真的很小
I can't get another job.
我找不到其他工作
I'm sorry to hear that.
那可真遺憾
Is there anything I can do to help?
我能幫你點什麼嗎?
You? No.
你嗎? 不
You've done enough.
你做的夠多了
- Wha... - I've been thinking about that day that I lost my key card,
- 什... - 我一直在回想我丟掉門卡的那天
and you're the last person that I remember having it with.
你是我記憶中最後一個拿過它的人
What,you don't think I stole it,do you?
什麼 你該不會懷疑我偷了它吧?
- Why would I steal your key card? - Nothing about that day makes sense.
- 我幹嘛要偷你的門卡? - 那天所有事都很不對勁
- I had full access to the museum. - I'm just here to get some answers and...
- 我有博物館的完全訪問權限 - 我只是來問點問題 然後...
I was hoping to get a letter from Agent Burke stating my complete innocence.
我希望能夠得到 Burke探員的證詞證明我清白
- There he is.- Uh,yeah,that's-- that's a really bad idea.
- 他就在那兒 - 是的 那可...真是個壞主意
He is swamped on a new case right now and just not in a giving mood.
他剛剛陷入一件新案子 心情不大好
Anyway,he wasn't even in charge of the Gershon investigation.
況且 他甚至都不是Gershon調查案的負責人
- Then who was? - That would be Agent Gruetzner.
- 那麼誰是呢? - 應該是Gruetzner探員
Art Crimes.He's not at these offices.
藝術罪案 他不在這些辦公室裡
So where do I find this Agent...
那我該去哪找這位...
- Gruetzner? - Gruetzner.
- Gruetzner? - Gruetzner
he is in the field today.
他今天出現場
But I could set something up for tomorrow.
不過我可以安排明天的會面
- All right. - All right?
- 好的 - 好的?
- Tomorrow. - Okay.
- 那就明天 - 好
Let me give you my number. You can text me the address.
我把手機號給你 你發短信告訴我地址
We're the FBI. We have your number.
我們可是FBI 我們有你的電話號
- I'll get you that letter.
我會給你那份證詞的
What's the story?
事情怎麼樣了?
Sergei Turgenev.
Sergei Turgenev
Our smooth-talking friend from the ice rink.
室內溜冰場裡的三寸不爛之舌
Got that from a friend at FAPSI
我從國家通信與信息局的朋友那裡拿到的
- That's Russian intelligence. - Russian intelligence.
- 那是俄國情報局 - 俄國情報局
Yeah,this is the Crime And Punishment of rap sheets.
是的 這簡直是是警局刑事檔案的"罪與罰"
And this guy...is worse.
這個傢伙... 比那還糟
That's Sergei's cousin Nikolai. Wanted for murder in Russia.
那是Sergei的表兄Nikolai 在俄國因殺人受到通緝
Money laundering,drug trafficking,arms trafficking,human trafficking.
洗錢 毒品走私 軍火走私 人販子
Basically,any kind of trafficking.Yeah.
基本上來說 包含了一切走私
Nobody knew he was in the country until now.
目前為止沒有人知道他在我國
We don't give visas to criminals,so either he snuck in on a tuna boat...
我們不給罪犯發籤證 所以要麼他是坐金槍魚捕獵船偷渡來的...
Or he flew here first-class using one of Sergei's passports.
要麼他是用Sergei的 某個護照坐一等艙飛來的
Question is...
問題在於...
if Sergei can bring Nikolai in here without us knowing,who else is he planning to import?
如果Sergei能在我們眼皮底下偷渡 Nikolai 那他是否還計劃帶別人進來?
If I had known about this,
如果我早知道這個
you could be playing hockey with Sergei
那你早就能跟Sergei一起打曲棍球了
instead of learning the difference between a lutz and a salchow.
而不是學習後外鉤點冰一周跳 和後內結環一周跳(花樣滑冰術語)的區別了
All right,don't you worry about me.
好吧 你別擔心我的事了
You just focus on becoming a top sports agent.
還是關注一下 怎麼做一個頂級體育經紀人吧
Con men taking 10%?
拿10%分紅的騙子?
I think I can handle it.
我覺得我能搞定
Okay,let me get this straight.
好吧 咱們把話說清楚
You need to become an expert figure skating coach in a day?
你得在一天內成為專業花樣滑冰教練?
No,I just need to look the part and learn enough to pass muster.
不 我只需要學一部分 夠在集合的時候矇混過關就夠了
So...what can you tell me?
那... 你能告訴我點什麼?
- Me? - Yeah.
- 我? - 對
- You want me to coach you to become a coach?
- 你想讓我教你怎麼做教練? - 是的
Honey,you have watched enough figure skating
親愛的 你看了夠多花樣滑冰了
to do color commentary on the next world championship.
多得夠在下次世界錦標賽上做解說了
Yeah,that's what we call an armchair expert.
是的 那就叫做紙上談兵
Honey,that is a world away from actually doing it.
親愛的 距離真正去做尚且有距離
You remember-- first time I was on the ice,- it was our second date.
你記得 我第一次滑冰 那是咱們第二次約會
How could I forget?
我怎麼可能忘?
You were supposed to teach me.
你本該教我來著
Well,how could I?You were sprawled out on the ice like Bambi...
我怎麼教你啊? 你一上冰就像小鹿斑比一樣四腳朝天...
and looking just as adorable.
不過還是很可愛
Good save.
補救得好
All right,this is what we're gonna do.We're gonna start with the basics.
好吧 接下來我們這麼做 從最基礎的部分開始
Then we're gonna move to Tonya Harding and Nancy Kerrigan,hopefully by midnight.
然後是Tonya Harding和Nancy Kerrigan 希望在午夜前看完
Uh-huh,and then one day,I will finally teach you how to skate.
嗯 到了白天 我就終於可以教你怎麼滑冰了
Oh,no,you're gonna teach me how to skate as soon as this case is over.
哦不 這案子一結你就教我吧
How do I look?
我看起來如何
Like an FBI accountant.
像個FBI的會計師
Agent Gruetzner's conservative attire is just an attempt to disguise
Gruetzner探員保守的打扮 只是一種掩飾的行為
his subversive and bohemian proclivities.
掩飾他具有破壞性的放蕩的癖性
don't overplay this,Moz.It is not dinner theatre.
別太過火 Moz 這不是晚間小劇場
You just need to answer a few simple questions.
你只需要回答一點簡單的問題
I'm a master improviser.
我是個即興發揮大家
I will be the perfect exigent supervisor.
我會是個完美的緊急情況監管者
That sounds familiar.
聽起來很耳熟
Yeah,it's not the first time the suit's gotten under my skin.
是的 這不是我第一次假扮探員
I just heard from the exigent supervisor.
我剛從緊急情況監管者那裡聽來
Looks like Sergei wants to meet at a vodka bar tomorrow,and that's a problem.
似乎Sergei打算明天在一個 伏特加酒吧會面 這帶來個問題
I need to be in Little Odessa at the same time I promised Rebecca a meeting with you.
安排Rebecca與你的會面的同時 我還得出現在小奧德賽
You say problem,I say opportunity.
你覺得是問題 我反而覺得是機會
You'll be off leash.
你就不會被監控
You can slip away,and big brother will be none the wiser.
你可以溜走 他們卻不知道
True.
這也是
Do we have an office yet?
我們弄好辦公室了嗎?
Yeah,and it's not far.
有 而且不遠
Dr. Gravich,my former chiropractor and hero to ambulance chasers everywhere
Gravich醫生 我的前任脊椎按摩師 也是唯利是圖者的英雄
takes his entire staff out to lunch from 1:00 until 2:00 every day.
每天中午一到兩點 都會帶全體員工出去吃午餐
A chiropractor's office?
一間脊椎按摩師的辦公室?
With some posters and sundry accoutrements,it'll look the part.
在用些海報和各式裝備 看上去就像了
And to keep her from asking too many questions,we can show her the Codex.
為了不讓她問太多 我們可以讓她看看法典
- She is a Mosconi expert. - That's why she started working at the museum.
- 她可是研究莫斯克尼的專家 - 所以她本來在圖書館工作
- Until you got her fired.
直到你害她失業了
- Maybe she'll forgive us if we give her a little peek at our chapter.
如果我們讓她看一看法典 它就會原諒我們
So you can reward her for your misdeed by having her reward us with her information.
所以你可以通過讓她提供信息 而彌補自己對她的過失
- Hello?
有人嗎?
Here comes one of our accoutrements now.
我們的有力武器來啦
Say hello to the Art Crimes Division's comely receptionist.
來和藝術品犯罪部門的 迷人的接待員打個招呼
FBI. May I help you?
這是聯邦調查局 有什麼可以幫到您的?
All right.
好吧
All right,Jones and the tac team are in a van a few blocks away.
好吧 Jones和特別行動小組 在幾個街區外的貨車上
Any closer and I think it'd be too risky.
再靠近的話就危險了
Yeah,no riskier than you after half a bottle of vodka.
也比不上喝了半支伏特加的你危險
- What? - Which is why I made these.
- 什麼? - 所以我做了這個
No,look-- no tricks.- What?
- 不 不耍花樣 - 什麼?
- I can handle myself. - Really?
- 我自己應付得了 - 真的嗎?
- Yes. - When was the last time you did a shot?
- 真的 - 你上次喝它是什麼時候?
I don't-- It was Hughes's retirement party.
我沒... 那是Hughes的退休派對
- We did three of them. - Ooh,three?
- 我們喝了三杯 - 哦 三杯?
- Yes. - Well,in Russia it's customary to drink until the bottle is empty.
- 是的 - 在俄羅斯 要喝就喝一整支的
Okay?This will keep us sober without insulting Sergei.
這能讓你在不冒犯Sergei的前提下 保持清醒
I don't need your trick glasses.
我不需要你的把戲杯
No problem,but,uh,I probably shouldn't walk in there with this.
沒問題 但 我最好不要帶著這個進去
Thank you.
謝謝
He isn't here.
他不在這
Neal Caffrey! You bastard.
Neal Caffrey! 你這個混蛋
I dated his sister. The ballerina.
我以前和她妹妹約會 她是個芭蕾舞女
Why does your love life always end up affecting me?
為什麼你的情史總會影響到我?
Get him out of here before he blows our cover.
在他暴露我們身份之前快把他弄走
- And wait for me right outside.
然後在外面等我
Dimitri!
Dimitri!
- So good to see you. - You never call my sister.
- 見到你真好 - 你從沒打電話給我妹妹
- I should kill you. - All right,okay.
- 我真該宰了你 - 好了 好了
Take it easy now,all right?
別在意了 好吧?
You and I both know I was one of many.
你我心知肚明我不過是大多數中的一人
What do you mean,One of many""?"My sister is a saint.
你什麼意思"大多數中的一人" 我妹妹很純的
- How was that? - It was perfect.
- 演得怎樣? - 堪稱完美
- It could not have gone better. - Was the accent too thick?
- 已經是最好的了 - 口音會不會太重?
No,it wasn't.It was great.
不 不 很好了
You're gonna nail that Fiddler On The Roof audition.
你肯定可以搞定 "屋頂上的提琴手"的試鏡
- Thanks. - Break legs,kid.
- 謝謝 - 加油 孩子
Hey,I ditched the anklet and Peter.I'm on my way.
嘿 我甩掉Peter和腳銬了 我現在過來
Where is your fast-talking friend?
你那個巧舌如簧的朋友呢?
Oh,something urgent came up.
他有要緊事
You know agents-- always putting out fires.
你知道經紀人的... 總在處理危機
Uh,bring us the caviar,shashlik,and a plate of pickled mushrooms.
我們要魚子醬 烤羊肉串 還有一碟醃蘑菇
- So,Peter Nevins. - Yeah?
- 所以你叫Peter Nevins - 是的
Figure skating coach to the stars.
明星們的滑冰教練
Nikolai.
Nikolai
There is just one little problem.
只是有個小問題
What's that?
怎麼了?
You don't seem to exist.
你似乎並不存在
Now,how can you be famous if you don't exist?
你要是不存在的話 怎麼可能很出名?
That's true.
這倒不假
Peter "Neevens" doesn't exist.
Peter "Neevens" 確實不存在
But...Peter Nevins-- N-E-V-I-N-S-- he does.
但是... Peter Nevins-- N-E-V-I-N-S 就存在了
It's an understandable mistake.
小失誤 可以理解
If I were put in front of a cyrillic alphabet keyboard,
如果給我個西裡爾字母的鍵盤
I'd-- Well,I wouldn't-- I wouldn't be able to get past na zdorovie.
我也... 我也拼不出"為我們的健康"
Na zdorovie.
為我們的健康
You'd think Art Crimes would call for a more aesthetically pleasing setup,
你可能覺得藝術品犯罪部門 需要更優雅的環境
but we take a backseat to Wall Street.
但我們選了個華爾街附近的地方
Good afternoon,Agent Caffrey.
下午好 Caffrey探員
And this is June.
這位是June
Our office couldn't function without her.
沒了她我們就做不了事了
- He's not exaggerating.
他可沒有誇大
- Ms.Lowe.Agent Gruetzner.We've been expecting you.
Lowe女士 Gruetzner特工 我們正在等你
I filled Agent Gruetzner in on our talk.
我和Gruetzner探員說過了
I'm sorry for any problems the Bureau may have caused.
我為局裡為你造成的麻煩感到抱歉
I have the letter you requested,along with my card,
我有你要的證明信 還有我的名片
in case any potential employers need to call to verify.
以備任何潛在僱主核實所用
Thank you.
謝謝
but I'm still looking for closure.
但我還希望有個了結
I have some questions.
我還有一些疑問
Could we,um,speak privately?
我們可以私下談談嗎?
Actually,there's something we'd like to talk to you about.
實際上 我們也有些事想和你談談
- You're married,yes? - Yeah.
- 你已經結婚了嗎? - 是的
- Happily. - That's good.
- 很幸福 - 那就好
Because Katya is a woman many men desire.
因為Katya是許多男人夢寐以求的
She once had a coach who was single.
她以前有個單身的教練
They would spend hours practicing,often late into the night.Very late.
他們總是練習 有時候練到晚上 非常晚
He no longer skates so well.
他現在已經不能怎麼滑冰了
Well,you should see what my wife does to me when I miss dinner.
那你該看看我錯過晚餐後 我妻子怎麼對我的
- That's good. - Yeah.
- 那很好 - 是的
- Well,sometimes.
- 有時候吧
But the Codex has been hidden away its entire existence.
但法典已經被藏到不知道哪了
The owner strictly forbade anyone from opening it.
法典主人嚴禁任何人翻閱它
How-- how did you get a copy?
你... 你們怎麼弄到複印件的?
That's classified.
這是機密
I'm afraid you're on a need-to-know basis.
恐怕對你只能按需知會
As in,we need to know what you know and not the other way around.
我們要知道你所知道的 而你不能反過來
If you're willing,the FBI would like your assistance deciphering its meaning.
若你願意 聯邦調查局需要你的協助 來破解它的含義
It could help us solve a very serious case.
它能幫我們解決一個重大案件
There is one small matter that you need to be made aware of.
但還有一件事你必須知道
There's a dangerous criminal who wants the information in the Codex,
有個非常危險的罪犯想知道法典的內容
and we need to figure out why.
我們想知道是為什麼
And time is of the essence.
而且時間很緊迫
You know what?You drink like Russian.
你知道嗎? 你喝起來像個俄國人
- Thank you. - Well,almost.
- 謝謝 - 差不多了
You start tomorrow.
你明天開工
Tomorrow's good.
明天很好
Good. Good.
很好 很好
Now,let me give you some advice.
現在  給你點建議
Stay on the ice and out of my business.
只管滑冰 別插手我的事
Understood.
明白
So a dangerous criminal is interested in the Mosconi Codex?
這麼說 有個危險的罪犯 對這本莫斯克尼法典感興趣?
We just wouldn't want to put you in harm's way unless you knew what you were getting into.
我們只是不想 讓你在不知情的情況下鋌而走險
The FBI will protect you.
FBI會保護你的
Look,I know I might just seem like another bookworm to you guys,but I can hold my own.
我知道 你們可能覺得我只是個會唸書的人 但我也不是沒腦子
I just need time to think about it.
給我點時間考慮一下
You have my card.Call with your decision.Just make it soon.
你有我的名片 想好了就給我打電話 但是要快
- Every minute counts. - I'll go down with you.
- 時間很緊 - 我送你下去
Thank you.
謝謝
We got two minutes!
還有兩分鐘!
Neal?
Neal?
How'd it go?
嗨 怎樣了?
I told you to wait right outside.
說了讓你就在外面等
Yeah,I figured you could use some coffee after all that vodka.
沒錯 我想你喝完那麼多伏特加之後 再來杯咖啡比較好
I found a great little place down the street.Amazing Tula gingerbread.
這條街走到頭 有家很棒的咖啡館 圖拉餅很好吃
- Are you inebriated? - No,I'm not inebriated.
- 你醉了嗎? - 沒 我沒醉
Here.Get the car.You're driving.
給 車給你 你來開
You know how alcohol tends to amplify certain personality traits?
你知道酒精會放大 人的某些個性特徵嗎?
- Get the car,Neal. - I'm on it.
- 開車去 Neal - 我這就去
Good work on that Peter Nevins bio.
Peter Nevins的簡歷做得不錯
It's a good thing they didn't check five minutes earlier.
要是他們再早5分鐘搜索 就要壞事了
We were still uploading.
那時候還在上傳呢
Neal took off,didn't he?
Neal遛了 是吧?
Yeah,he sure did.
當然
I wanted to follow,but I didn't want to leave you in there with Sergei.
我是想跟著他的 但我不能留你和Sergei單獨一起
Find out where he went.
查查他去了哪
Will do.
我會的
Morning.
早
- Time for breakfast? - Uh,I'm running late.
- 吃早飯嗎? - 我要遲到了
I've got a stack of ASAC files the size of an oddly shaped child.
我那還堆著山一樣高的文件呢
You know,when we,um,we talked about this job,I was actually thinking,"Wow...
知道嗎 當初... 當初我們說起 你的新工作 我一直以為是...
"Predictable schedule.
"哇 無突發行程安排
Reasonable hours.
工作時間合理"
"And now it's back to late nights and early mornings and vodka rooms.
但現在又變成了是晝伏夜出 居然還要灌伏特加
To say nothing about the figure skaters in short skirts.
更別提那些 穿短裙的花樣滑冰小姑娘了
Well,she's not my type.
她不是我的菜
I'm more into the Bambi kind of thing.
我更喜歡斑比的這種
Mm,the uncoordinated limbs sprawled.
嗯 肢體不協調 東倒西歪
Exactly.
沒錯
You okay?
你沒事吧?
Hon...
親愛的...
every day you're in the field...
你每天出任務的時候...
every day,I...
每天 我都...
I can't exhale until I hear you walk through that door at night.
直到晚上聽見你進了門 我才能鬆下一口氣
And I don't like that feeling.
我不喜歡這樣
Agent Siegel's murder was a random act of violence.
Siegel探員的死 是一場意外的暴力事件
Could have happened to anybody.
這種事可能發生在任何人身上
But it's not gonna happen to me.
可它不會發生在我身上
I promise.
我保證
We good?
好了嗎?
Can't wait to hear your notes on how to improve that.
真是等不及要聽你的改進建議了
I don't have to give notes.
我可不用給建議
I only have to pretend to give notes.
我只要假裝給建議就好
Mm,kneeling at the anklet of the master has taught you well.
嗯 臨陣抱佛腳 效果還可以嘛
The master is chewing gum?
大師在嚼口香糖?
I'm getting into character.
大師正在進入角色
- I'm Neal Micali.
我是Neal Micali
He chews gum when he's nervous.
他緊張的時候會嚼口香糖
I don't need a backstory.
我可不用什麼人物背景
I'm gonna go try to find Sergei's passport workshop.
我去找找Sergei的護照作坊
make it quick. Sergei doesn't like anyone nosing around.
那你最好快點 Sergei不喜歡別人亂晃
Save your coaching for the ice.
把你的說教留在滑冰場上吧
You ready,coach?
準備好了嗎 教練?
Yeah.
是的
You can trust us.
你可以相信我們
But you have to tell me everything about Sergei's business.
但你得告訴我 所有關於Sergei生意的情況
All I know is that he brings terrible people to Little Odessa.
我只知道他帶了一群可怕的人 去了小奧德賽
He wants to control it.
他想要控制那裡
Everyone is scared of him.
每個人都很怕他
Then why are you with him?
那你為什麼要跟他一夥?
In the beginning,he was a good man.
起初他是個好人
I moved from Moscow to be with him.
我離開莫斯科就是為了跟他在一起
Now he treats me like possession.
現在他對我就像對待私人物品一樣
Last week,he thought I cheated on him.
上周他覺得我對他不忠
So he... hit me.
所以就... 打了我
And the next day,like nothing happened,he asks me to marry him.
隔天他又像什麼都沒發生一樣 向我求婚
What did you say?
你怎麼回答的?
If I say yes...
如果我答應他
I'll be miserable forever.
我會痛苦一輩子
And if I say no...
但如果我說不
I'm dead.
我就死定了
You're my coach.
你是我的教練
You have advice?
你有什麼建議?
Piotr!
Piotr!
Sergei.
Sergei
I didn't expect you here so early.
我沒想到你這麼早就來了
You think I could just let you coach the love of my life without a little observation?
你以為我會讓你在沒有監管的情況下 給我最愛的人做輔導嗎?
I'm curious to know what you think.
我想知道你是怎麼看的
So Katya's had trouble executing her salchow.
Katya在她的沙克跳上有點困難
In my opinion,the problem is her center of gravity when she lands on the inside edge.
在我看來問題出在 她內點冰落地時的重心
Well,that would be a problem.
這確實是個問題
The salchow always lands on the outside edge.
沙克跳一直是外點冰落地的
All she needs is a slight adjustment.
她只要稍微調整一下就可以了
The extension of her free foot on the three spin tends to be a bit shallow.
在三周自由旋轉時 她的活動腳延伸得還不夠
Okay.Work your magic.
好吧 繼續發揮你的神奇力量
Now,listen,make sure that you keep that extension long.
聽我說 你要確保拖足夠長的時間
Think long.
想長遠一些
Go skate.
去滑吧
Trust yourself,all right?
相信你自己 好嗎?
Don't forget to keep an eye on this guy.
別忘了看著點這個男人
And push.
然後用力
Not bad. Not bad.
不錯 不錯
But not perfect either.
但還不夠完美
In competition,you gotta be flawless.
在比賽裡你必須做到無可挑剔
We'll keep working on it.
我們要繼續訓練這部分
Don't go easy on her.She needs to learn discipline.
別太縱容她 她需要有些紀律性
Uh,Sergei.I got my hockey skates in the bag.
Sergei我包裡有冰球鞋
Katya can take a break while I give you a few pointers.
讓Katya休息一下 我來給你教幾手
That's why you Americans are losing your edge.All play and no work.
這就是為什麼你們美國人失去了優勢 只顧著玩 不幹正事
Oh,okay.I get it,I get it.
哦 好吧 我明白了 明白了
You don't want a repeat of miracle on ice.
你們並不想在冰場上再創奇跡
The US kicks Russia's ass again.
美國人再次擊敗俄國人
That's an open wound for many of my countrymen,Peter.
那是我們國家許多人的傷心事 Peter
- Get my skates. See you on the ice. - Excellent.
- 拿我的冰鞋來 咱們冰上見 - 好極了
Bingo.
找到了
Jack,that is the same line that you sold Katarina...in Brussels in '97,all right?
Jack 這是你在97年布魯塞爾站 你賣給Katarina的同一款式
- Hey,you.- Hey,my cell phone died.All right?Can I-- Do you mind?
- 嘿! - 我手機沒電了 我能... 借用一下?
Hey,pal,listen,I'm jetlagged,all right?
夥計 聽著 我還倒時差呢
So let's close this out,or I'm gonna have to call your competition.
我們直接解決吧 否則我只好去找你的競爭對手
Out.Now.
出去 馬上
Do you know what this is?
你知道這是什麼嗎?
It's a deal memo for Katya.
這是Katya合約的條款備忘錄
A generous salary,bonuses and bumps,travel,food,lodging,wardrobe.Now,get lost.
豐厚的薪水 獎金 旅行 美食 居所 服裝 現在 你出去
Or you can explain to Sergei why Katya will be crying into her sequins all night.
否則你就向Sergei解釋 Katya整晚掉眼淚的原因
Yeah,I'm back.Sorry.
是 我聽著呢 抱歉
Hold on,Jack.
稍等 Jack
Two minutes.I come back,you be gone.
兩分鐘時間 在我回來之前消失
All right.
好的
Yeah.Yeah,I'm still here.
是 是 我在
Just,uh,cleaning my ears out from all the manure
我已經聽了你十分鐘的廢話
you've been shoveling into them for the last ten minutes.
現在我的耳朵需要清靜一下
Oh,it's nice showing you how it's done.
很榮幸給你做示範
Four out of five,Peter.
五球進四 Peter
- I wish you good luck. - Thank you.
- 祝你好運 - 謝謝
Keep your eye on the puck.
看準球再打
That's one.
第一個
Not too bad.
不錯啊
But we're playing best of three.
但是我們三局兩勝
Oh,let's make it best of five.
五局三勝好了
Vanya.
Vanya
Seryozha.
Seryozha
What the hell was that?
怎麼回事?
That one got away.
打偏了
You know what? You're a crazy person.
你就是個瘋子
But I like that.
但是我喜歡
I'll finish with you tomorrow.I have business to take care of.
我們明天接著打 現在我有生意要做
Ivan made bail.
Ivan被保釋了
Why wasn't I told about this?
我怎麼不知道?
The court dropped the ball.
法庭失職了
Someone didn't get the memo that we've got an open investigation.
沒人看到我們有在查案件的備忘提醒
By the way,Gretzky,did you mean for the puck to hit the wall,
說到這裡 冰球明星 你是故意擊中圍欄
or were you trying to hit Sergei and missed?
還是想打Sergei卻打偏了?
You should come to the firing range.
你該到靶場看看
- Trust me. He never misses. - Thank you.
- 相信我 他從不失手 - 謝謝
The names on the printout Neal grabbed match fugitives on the Russian intel watch list.
Neal拿到的資料 和俄羅斯情報局的逃犯名單吻合
Calls between the ice rink and Moscow shot up in the past week.
上周冰場和莫斯科之間的通話次數很多
Looks like Sergei's bringing in new recruits.
看來Sergei在招新人啊
They'll be untraceable the minute they get through customs with new identities. - Yes?
一旦用新身份通過海關 就再也沒辦法追查到他們了
So if we don't crack Sergei's network soon,
- 什麼事? - 如果不盡快搗毀Sergei的組織
a bunch of hardened Russian criminals will go into the wind on US soil.
大批俄羅斯重罪罪犯將湧進美國境內
Seems like enough of them already have. Come on.
已經進來夠多的了 走吧
Ivan was pulled out of the East River this morning by NYPD.
今天早晨紐約警局在東河發現Ivan的屍體
They didn't trust him not to talk.
他們還是選擇了殺人滅口
Russian intelligence agreed to extradite all of Sergei's men who were already in New York.
俄羅斯情報局同意 將Sergei目前在紐約的手下引渡回國
With the clean passports,they're gonna be almost impossible to find.
有新的身份 幾乎不可能找到他們
We've dealt with money laundering before,but Sergei's laundering people.
我們之前處理過洗錢的案件 但是Sergei是"洗"人啊
So...how do we round up a bunch of fearless Russians who are scattered throughout the city?
我們怎麼抓捕這些散佈在紐約 還肆無忌憚的俄羅斯人?
Before they tip each other off.
還得在他們通風報信之前
It's gonna take a lot of manpower and a lot of preparation,and we're running out of time.
這需要大量的人力 充足的準備工作 可是時間不夠用了
What if Sergei brings him to us?
如果讓Sergei主動將他們交出來呢?
I'm listening.
說下去
Well,what's the one thing his guys can't resist?
這些人最無法抗拒的是什麼?
An excuse to party.
聚會的理由
So let's give them something to celebrate.
所以我們就找個理由 讓他們好好慶祝一下
Okay.
好
Maybe provide Sergei with the answer - he's been waiting for. - Katya?
- 也許可以給Sergei那個他一直等待的答案 - Katya?
What kind of fiance would he be if he didn't throw a party to celebrate -
人生最開心的一天都不慶祝的話
the happiest day of his life? - Nice.
- 這算什麼未婚夫啊 - 漂亮
He would not be a good one. That's excellent.
確實不夠格 好極了
We put them all together in one place at the same time,
把他們同時召集在一個地方
and we put an end to Sergei's grip on Little Odessa.
還能幫小奧德賽擺脫Sergei的魔掌
I'll do it.
我會照做的
All right,Katya,I will make sure that nothing happens to you.
好的 Katya 我保證你不會有事的
But I need to know from you if you are really up for this.
可是我需要知道 你是不是真的準備好了
I woke up at 5:00 every morning as a child.
我還是孩子的時候 就要每天早晨5點起床
Walked to the gym in the snow six miles away.
在雪中走6英里才能到體育館
At practice,my toes bled in my skates.
練習的時候 我的腳趾在冰鞋中流血
But I put on a smile every day.
但是我每天都保持著微笑
This is nothing.
這根本不算什麼
Sergei!
Sergei!
Peter helped me see how stupid I have been.
Peter讓我認清曾經的自己是多麼愚蠢
I can't believe it has taken me so long.
真不敢相信 自己竟然花了這麼久的時間才決定
Yes...
我願意...
I will marry you!
我要嫁給你!
Tonight,we celebrate.
就今天晚上 慶祝一下
He has a lot of friends.
他朋友真夠多的
They can't all be criminals.
不會全是罪犯吧
We'll do some weeding at headquarters.
回了總部再逐個判斷
Peter!
Peter!
Come here.
過來
I'm so glad you could make it. I was hoping to meet your lovely wife.
很高興你能來 我還想著能見到你的妻子呢
Ah,she sends her regrets. She came down with the flu.
代她表示歉意 流感 只好臥床休息
Ah,too bad. Maybe at the wedding. - Maybe.
- 太遺憾了 只好在婚禮上見了 - 也許吧
Your cousin isn't sticking around for the celebration?
你的表弟不留下來慶祝嗎?
Life is a place of service.Do you read Tolstoy?
"無奔波 不生活" 你們讀過托爾斯泰嗎?
Ah,War And Peace,one of my favorites.
"戰爭與和平" 我的最愛之一
Ah,enough talk.
別光顧著說話
Let's celebrate.
來慶祝吧
Nikolai's leaving.
Nikolai要走了
Stall him.
拖住他
- I want him to be here for her engagement present. - But I'll miss your speech.
- 我要他在這裡當她的訂婚禮物 - 可是我就錯過你的精彩演說啦
- I'll make sure somebody records it. - You better.
- 會有人錄下來的 - 最好這樣
Uh,excuse me.Excuse me.I'm sorry. Excuse me.
打擾一下 抱歉 打擾一下
I'm Peter Nevins.
我是Peter Nevins
None of you know me,but I am Katya's coach.
你們都不認識我 我是Katya的教練
And I just want to congratulate my new friend Sergei and his lovely,talented fiance Katya.
我想在此祝福我的朋友Sergei 以及他可愛動人 極具天賦的未婚妻 Katya
Hey,buddy!
嘿 老兄!
It's Neal Micali.
我是Neal Micali
Come on,the party's just getting started. Where's the fire,my man?
別走啊 聚會剛剛開始 什麼事這麼急啊 朋友?
Hey,I feel like we got off to a bad start.
我覺得我們的相識不怎麼愉快
How about you and me go back up there,have a shot or three-- What do you say?
現在我們回去喝個幾杯 怎麼樣?
So what I'm really trying to say is,it's good to put all these names to faces.
我想說的是 能認識大家真好
So raise a glass.
舉杯
Oh,one other thing.
還有件事
You're all under arrest.
你們都被捕了
FBI!Nobody move!Hands in the air!
FBI! 不許動! 舉起手來!
- Get down!
趴下!
You're no sport agent.
你根本不是什麼運動員經紀人
Yeah,and you're not Sammy Jordache？Really?
是啊 你也不是什麼Sammy Jordache 這也可以?
- Don't even think about it.
想都別想!
Back away.
退後
- Just put it down right now. - Back away.
- 趕緊放下 - 退後
- Put that knife down right now! -I'm taking her with me!
-馬上把刀放下 -我要帶她走
You got five guns on you right now!Put it down!
有五支槍指著你 趕緊放下
You okay?
你沒事吧
You were right.
你說得對
Peter Nevins doesn't exist.
沒有Peter Nevins這個人
By the looks of it...
但看上去...
neither do any of these people.
這些人也不存在
Remember my face.
你給我記著
Get him out of here.
帶他出去
So...
所以...
- off to Innsbruck. - Yes.
- 去Innsbruck - 是
- That should be an adventure,huh? - Oh,I hope so.
- 會是場好冒險吧 - 希望如此
Any last advice,coach?
有什麼最後的建議嗎 教練
Watch your leading edge on the double axel
注意兩周半跳時的著力邊
and be sure to not lock your knees on the Biellmann spin.
貝爾曼旋轉時膝蓋不要僵
Oh,you have no idea what any of that means,do you?
你壓根不知道自己在說什麼 是吧
No.A commentator once said it on my research DVDs.It sounded good.
嗯 在我看DVD學習時 一個評論員說的 聽上去不錯
Thank you.
謝謝你
Sure.
不客氣
Good luck.
祝你好運
- I'll walk you out. - Thank you.
- 我送你出去 - 謝謝
Bye.
拜拜
What'd you find?
你發現了什麼
Surveillance cameras a block from the vodka room led us to a cabbie.
伏特加房間一街區外的攝像頭 讓我們找到了一輛計程車
He picked them up and brought them in.
他接上了他們到這裡
Anything special about the place?
那裡有什麼特別的嗎
Nah,it's just your average office building.
和你的辦公樓一樣
Accountants,therapists,nothing out of the ordinary.
會計 醫生 沒什麼奇怪的
Is there any reason he'd slip away to come here?
有什麼理由他要溜來這裡嗎
Neal always has a reason.
Neal總會有理由的
You can pull the ripcord on your safety chute.
你可以拉開緩降器的安全索了
Rebecca just called on the burner phone.
Rebecca剛剛打給了一次性手機
Really?What did she say?
是嗎 她說什麼
Do I detect a lilt in your voice?
聽起來你很開心
Agent Gruetzner sees all.
Gruetzner洞察一切
You like her.
你喜歡她
What is this,sixth grade?
這是什麼 六年級辦家家嗎
Personally,I don't see the attraction.
說實話 我不覺得她有吸引力
She doesn't want to rob you or arrest you or charge you with insurance fraud.
她不想搶你 逮捕你 或是收你保費
Just tell me what she said.
告訴我她說了什麼
She wants to meet at the Rare Book Room.
她想在珍本書室見你
You know,there's nothing more enchanting than a beautiful woman
那裡沒有什麼
cradling a classic opus in her soft,gentle hands.
比一個美女用她柔軟纖細的雙手 呵護經典作品更吸引人了
Would you like to take the lead on this one?
你要主動出擊嗎
No,you're the front man.I'm merely rhythm guitar.
不 你是前鋒 我只是伴奏的吉他
Yeah,well,so was John Lennon.
列儂也是一樣
Thank you for that.
謝謝你
Leave your heart off your sleeve.
別陷得太深
- Can I help you? - Yeah.
- 有什麼我能幫你的嗎 - 當然
Uh,just a routine call.
只是例行訪問
We're checking all the offices in the area.
我們在查附近所有的辦公室
Anything unusual occur here in the last couple days?
最近幾天有沒有什麼特別的事發生
Not unless you consider a room full of herniated discs unusual.
沒什麼 除非你覺得 一間坐滿椎間盤突出病人的房間不正常
Mind if I poke around?
介意我隨便走走嗎
Honey,you go ahead and poke.
寶貝 你隨意
Hello,Dr.Gravich's office.How can I help you?
你好 Gravich醫生辦公室 您需要什麼幫助嗎
Well,what seems to be the problem?
有什麼問題嗎
how's Thursday?He's here from 10:00 AM till 5:00.
週四呢 他早上10點到下午5點都在
Okay.
好
You mind if I read over your shoulder?
介意我站在你背後讀嗎
it's not exactly light reading.
這可不是閒書
- Oh,Mosconi. - Yeah.
- 哦 莫斯克尼的 - 對
I figured we could,um,start our research.
我想我們可以開始研究了
Does that mean you've come to a decision?
這表示你決定了嗎
Yes,it does.
是的
I will help you with the Codex.
我會幫你研究法典
- but...I should tell you something first,just so you know. - Tell me.
- 但我得先告訴你件事 - 說吧
I,um...I did time.
我 我坐過牢
Really?
真的嗎
I was 19.It was a semester in Marrakesh.
我當時19歲 那是在 馬拉喀什(摩洛哥歷史古城)的一個學期
So I'm in the Menara Gardens,and there was this beautiful green tile.
我在Menara花園 那裡有一片很漂亮的綠瓷磚
What,in the Saadian Pavilion?
什麼 在薩阿迪王朝國家館嗎?
Yes.
是的
So it had fallen off the roof,and I pocketed it.
它從屋頂上掉下來 我把它裝進了口袋
And I always meant to take it back,and then when I tried... - You got pinched.
- 我總是想將它還回去 但當我想去的時候 - 你被抓了
It was the scariest night of my life.
那是我人生最恐怖的一晚
Um,I'm sorry,"Night"?Singular?
抱歉 一晚 只有一晚嗎
- Believe me... - One night in jail?
- 相信我... - 在監獄只有一晚
- One night in a Moroccan prison is enough. - All right.
- 在摩洛哥監獄待一晚就夠了 - 好的
Look...we've worked with ex-cons before.
我們和前科犯一起工作過
Even seasoned,hardened criminals,like yourself.
甚至包括慣犯 不知悔改的 就像你自己一樣
Did you have a prison bitch?
你有找人來服務自己嗎
Sorry.
抱歉
And,in the interest of full disclosure,I...
為了坦誠相待 我...
Look our copy of the Codex is incomplete.
我有的法典不全
How much do you have?
你有多少
A single chapter.It's chapter 13.
只有一章 第13章
Does that mean anything to you?
你有想到什麼嗎
- You know what? - What?
- 你知道嗎 - 什麼
I'm done with games.
我不想再陪你玩了
Games?What are you talking about?
玩 你在說什麼
I-- Did I say-- What did I say?
我 我說了什麼
Go ahead.Open it.Chapter 13.
打開它 第13章
No luck?
運氣不好嗎
Try this one.
試試這個
Mosconi was incredibly superstitious.
莫斯克尼非常迷信
In all the books he ever produced,he never wrote a chapter 13.
他所有的書裡都沒有第13章
That's it.
就是這樣
You're getting your sea legs back.
你可以站穩了
Frozen sea legs.
快凍僵了
Is it really okay that we're doing this?
我們真的可以這麼做嗎
Well,technically,it's a crime scene,so don't touch anything. - Okay.
- 其實這是個犯罪現場 所以什麼都別碰 - 好
All right,tell me how to turn again.
好 再告訴我一次怎麼旋轉
- All right,just put pressure on the outside blade And lean. - Yes.
- 把力量加在外側的冰刀上 傾斜 - 好
Oh,like that!
就像那樣
- There you go. - Yeah!
- 你做到了 - 太棒了
- Good.- Wait,wait-- whoa!
- 很好 - 等等
I got you.I got you.
有我在 我扶著你
- Okay. - I got you.
- 好 - 我在這
Yeah.You always do.
嗯 你一直都在
Okay.
好
Kind of like our second date.
好像我們的第二次約會
Little better.
比上次好點
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸園美劇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸園字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-静静的生活
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組=- 翻譯: Nancy 安 Zzinc 郭郭 塵沙 校對: 時差雪 時間軸: 靜靜的生活
white.collar.s05e06
妙警賊探 第五季 第六集